Hello, everyone. Welcome to a discussion
of effective communication, storytelling,
and brand, where we explore the
power of effective communication,
something that has long been an interest of mine, both as a scholar and as a leader.
You'll explore how storytelling can catalyze action, build credibility, and bring
our mission to life. And you'll learn
skills for creating messages that resonate
deeply with your audience as inspiring
trust and aligning our community with
Vanderbilt's vision. By honing these
skills, you'll not only help share our
narrative, you'll become
an important part of it.
Let's embrace this opportunity to collectively elevate our brand and build even
greater momentum on a path towards becoming the great university of the twenty-first
century.